<assertions>
	<assertion id="1" tag="ref:XBD7:46754:46754">
		Establish the connection between file and file descriptor.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="2" tag="ref:XBD7:46759:46760">
		When file is opened using open(), file descriptor shall not
		share with any other process with in the system.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="3" tag="ref:XBD7:46760:46761">
		FD_CLOEXEC file descriptor flag associated with the new file descriptor
		shall be cleared unless the O_CLOEXEC flag is set in oflag.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="4" tag="ref:XBD6:46763:46764">
		The file offset used to mark the current position within the file shall
		be set to the beginning of the file.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="5" tag="ref:XBD7:46770:46771">
		When O_EXEC flag is used, file is opened for execute only.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="6" tag="ref:XBD7:46772:46772">
		When O_RDONLY flag is used, file is opened for read only.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="7" tag="ref:XBD7:46773:46774">
		When O_RDWR flag is used, file is opened for read and write.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="8" tag="ref:XBD7:46775:46776">
		When O_SEARCH flag is used, directory is opened for search only.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="9" tag="ref:XBD7:46777:46777">
		When O_WRONLY flag is used, file is opened for write only.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="10" tag="ref:XBD7:46779:46779">
		When O_APPEND flag is used, the file offset shall be set to the end of
		the file prior to each write
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="11" tag="ref:XBD7:46781:46782">
		When O_CREAT flag is set and O_DIRECTORY flag is not set, the file shall
		be created as regular file.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="12" tag="ref:XBD7:46783:46784">
		When O_CREAT flag is set, the user ID of the file which is created,
		shall be set to the effective user ID of the process.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="13" tag="ref:XBD7:46784:46785">
		When O_CREAT flag is set, the group ID of the file which is created shall
		be set to the group ID of the file’s parent directory.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="14" tag="ref:XBD7:46786:46792">
		When O_CREAT flag is set, permission bits for the file mode which is
		created shall be set as (mode_t & ~umask), where mode_t is user argument
		which is passed after oflag.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="15" tag="ref:XBD7:46799:46799">
		When O_DIRECTORY flag and O_CREAT flag are set, new directory will be
		created if not already exist.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="16" tag="ref:XBD7:46799:46799">
		When O_DIRECTORY flag is set on non directory file, call will fail and
		set errno to [ENOTDIR]
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="17" tag="ref:XBD7:46800:46801">
		When O_DSYNC flag is set, Write I/O operations on the file descriptor
		shall complete as defined by synchronized I/O data integrity completion
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="18" tag="ref:XBD7:46802:46803">
		When O_CREAT and O_EXCL are set, open( ) shall fail if the file exists
		and errno will be set EEXIST.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="19" tag="ref:XBD7:46803:46806">
		When O_CREAT and O_EXCL are set, check for the existence of the file and
		the creation of the file if it does not exist shall be atomic with respect
		to other threads executing open( ) naming the same filename in the same
		directory with O_EXCL and O_CREAT set.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="20" tag="ref:XBD7:46807:46809">
		When O_EXCL and O_CREAT are set, and path names a symbolic link, open( )
		shall fail and set errno to [EEXIST], regardless of the contents of the symbolic link.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="21" tag="ref:XBD7:46810:46811">
		When O_NOCTTY is set and path identifies a terminal device, open( )
		shall not cause the terminal device to become the controlling terminal for the process.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="22" tag="ref:XBD7:46811:46812">
		When O_NOCTTY is set and if path does not identify a terminal device,
		O_NOCTTY shall be ignored.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="23" tag="ref:XBD7:46813:46813">
		When O_NOFOLLOW is set and If pathname is a symbolic link, then the
		open fail and set errno to [ELOOP]
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="24" tag="ref:XBD7:46814:46815">
		When opening a FIFO with O_RDONLY set and If O_NONBLOCK is set, an
		open( ) for reading-only shall return without delay.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="25" tag="ref:XBD7:46816:46817">
		When opening a FIFO with O_WRONLY set and if O_NONBLOCK is set, open( )
		for writing-only shall return an error if no process currently has the file open for reading.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="26" tag="ref:XBD7:46817:46818">
		When opening a FIFO with O_RDONLY set and If O_NONBLOCK is not set, an
		open( ) for reading-only shall block the calling thread until a thread opens the file for writing
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="27" tag="ref:XBD7:46818:46819">
		When opening a FIFO with O_WRONLY set and if O_NONBLOCK is not set,
		open( ) for writing-only shall block the calling thread until a thread opens the file for reading.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="28" tag="ref:XBD7:46822:46824">
		When opening a block special or character special files which
		supports non blocking opens with O_NONBLOCK set, the open( ) function
		shall return without blocking for the device to be ready or available.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="29" tag="ref:XBD7:46825:46828">
		When opening a block special or character special files which supports
		non blocking opens with O_NONBLOCK not set, the open( ) function shall block
		the calling thread until the device is ready or available before returning.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="30" tag="ref:XBD7:46843:46844">
		When O_TRUNC flag is set and If the file already exists and is a regular file and the access
		mode allows writing (i.e., is O_RDWR or O_WRONLY) it will be truncated to length 0.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="31" tag="ref:XBD7:46845:46846">
		When the file is a FIFO or terminal device file, the O_TRUNC flag is ignored.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="32" tag="ref:XBD7:">
		If path identifies a terminal device other than a pseudo-terminal, the
		device is not already open in any process, and either O_TTY_INIT is set in
		oflag or O_TTY_INIT has the value zero, open( ) shall set any non-standard
		termios structure terminal parameters to a state that provides conforming behavior.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="33" tag="ref:XBD7:46860:46861">
		When O_CREAT is set and the file did not previously exist, upon successful
		completion, open( ) shall mark for update the last data access, last data
		modification, and last file status change timestamps of the file and the last
		data modification and last file status change timestamps of the parent directory.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="34" tag="ref:XBD7:46866:46867">
		When O_TRUNC is set and the file did previously exist, upon successful completion, open( ) shall
		mark for update the last data modification and last file status change timestamps of the file.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="35" tag="ref:XBD7:46880:46881">
		The largest value that can be represented correctly in an object of type off_t shall be established
		as the offset maximum in the open file description.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="36" tag="ref:XBD7:46899:46899">
		When search permission is denied on a component of the path prefix, errno will be set to EACCES.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="37" tag="ref:XBD7:46900:46900">
		When the file exists and permission specified by oflag are denied, errno will be set to EACCES.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="38" tag="ref:XBD7:46901:46901">
		When the file does not exist and write permission are denied on directory, errno will be set to EACCES.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="39" tag="ref:XBD7:46902:46902">
		When O_TRUNC is set and write permission is denied, errno will be set to EACCES.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="40" tag="ref:XBD7:46904:46904">
		When a signal was caught during open(), errno will be set to EINTR.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="41" tag="ref:XBD7:46905:46905">
		When O_DSYNC is set and synchronized I/O is not supported on the file, errno will be set to  EINVAL.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="42" tag="ref:XBD7:46906:46907">
		When the path argument names a STREAMS file and a hangup or error occurred during the open( ), errno will be set EIO.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="43" tag="ref:XBD7:46908:46909">
		When the named file is a directory and oflag includes O_WRONLY or O_RDWR, or
		includes O_CREAT without O_DIRECTORY, errno will be set to EISDIR.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="44" tag="ref:XBD7:46910:46911">
		When a loop exists in symbolic links encountered during resolution of the path argument, errno will be set to ELOOP.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="45" tag="ref:XBD7:46913:46913">
		When all file descriptors available to the process are currently open, errno will be set EMFILE.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="47" tag="ref:XBD7:46914:46915">
		When the length of a component of a pathname is longer than {NAME_MAX}, errno will be set to ENAMETOOLONG.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="46" tag="ref:XBD7:46916:46916">
		When the maximum allowable number of files is currently open in the system, errno will be set to ENFILE
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="47" tag="ref:XBD7:46917:46917">
		When O_CREAT is not set and a component of path does not name an existing file, errno will be set to ENOENT.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="48" tag="ref:XBD7:46918:46919">
		When O_CREAT is set and a component of the path prefix of path does not name an existing file,
		or path points to an empty string, errno will be set to ENOENT.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="49" tag="ref:XBD7:46920:46922">
		When O_CREAT is set, and the path argument contains at least one non-slash character
		and ends with one or more trailing slash characters, errno will be set to ENOTDIR.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="50" tag="ref:XBD7:46923:46924">
		When O_CREAT flag is set and If the path without the trailing slash characters would
		name an existing file, an [ENOENT] error shall not occur.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="51" tag="ref:XBD7:46925:46926">
		When the path argument names a STREAMS-based file and the system is unable to allocate a STREAM,
		errno will be set to ENOSR.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="52" tag="ref:XBD7:46927:46928">
		When the directory or file system that would contain the new file cannot be expanded,
		the file does not exist, and O_CREAT is specified, errno will be set to ENOSPC.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="53" tag="ref:XBD7:46936:46937">
		When O_NONBLOCK is set, the named file is a FIFO, O_WRONLY is set, and no process has the file open for reading,
		errno will be set to ENXIO.
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="54" tag="ref:XBD7:46938:46939">
		When the named file is a character special or block special file, and the device associated with this special file
		does not exist, errno will be set to ENXIO
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="55" tag="ref:XBD7:46940:46941">
		When the named file is a regular file and the size of the file cannot be represented correctly in an object of
		type off_t, errno will be set to EOVERFLOW
	</assertion>
	<assertion id="56" tag="ref:XBD7:46942:46944">
		When the named file resides on a read-only file system and either O_WRONLY, O_RDWR,
		O_CREAT (if the file does not exist), or O_TRUNC is set in the oflag argument, errno will be set to EROFS
	</assertion>
</assertions>
