<assertions>
  <assertion id="1" tag="ref:XSH6:34849:34852">
   	The function shall apply a read lock to the read-write lock referenced by
   	rwlock as in the pthread_rwlock_rdlock(). However, if the lock cannot be
   	acquired wither out waiting for other threads to unlock the lock, this wait
   	shall be terminated when the specified timeout expires.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="2" tag="ref:XSH6:34852:34855">
	The timeout shall expire when the absolute time specified by abs_timeout passes,
	as measured by the clock on which timeouts are based (that is, when the
	value of that clock equals or exceeds abs_timeout), or if the absolute time
	specified by abs_timeout has already been passed at the time of the call.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="3" tag="ref:XSH6:34856:34856">
 	If the Timers option is supported, the timeout shall be based on the
	CLOCK_REALTIME clock.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="4" tag="ref:XSH6:34856:34859">
	If the Timers option is not supported, the timeout shall be based on the
	system clock as returned by the time( ) function. The resolution of the timeout
	shall be the resolution of the clock on which it is based. The timespec data type
	is defined in the 'time.h' header.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="5" tag="ref:XSH6:34859:34861">
	Under no circumstances shall the function fail with a timeout if the lock can be
	acquired immediately. The abs_timeout parameter need not be checked if the lock
	can be immediately acquired.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="6" tag="ref:XSH6:34862:34864">
	If a signal that causes a signal handler to be executed is delivered to
	a thread blocked on a read-write lock via a call to pthread_rwlock_timedwrlock( ),
	upon return from the signal handler the thread shall resume waiting for the lock
	as if it was not interrupted.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="7" tag="ref:XSH6:34868:34870">
	Shall return zero if the lock for writing on the read-write lock object
	referenced by rwlock is acquired. Otherwise, an error number shall be returned
	to indicate the error
	pthread_rwlock_timedwrlock( ) function shall fail if:
	[ETIMEDOUT] The lock could not be acquired before the specified timeout expired.
	The function shall not return an error code of [EINTR].
  </assertion>

</assertions>
