<assertions>
  <assertion id="1" tag="ref:XBD7:66766:66766">
    This function will convert the initial portion of the string pointed to by
    nptr to a type long.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="2" tag="ref:XBD7:66788:66790">
    If the input string is empty or consists entirely of white-space characters,
    or if the first non-white-space character is other than a sign or a permissible
    letter or digit:
        The subject sequence will contain no characters.
    A subject sequence is interpreted as an integer represented in some radix
    determined by the value of base.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="3" tag="ref:XBD7:66791:66792">
    If the subject sequence has the expected form and the value of base is 0:
        The sequence of characters starting with the first digit will be
        interpreted as an integer constant.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="4" tag="ref:XBD7:66792:66794">
    If the subject sequence has the expected form and the value of base is
    between 2 and 36:
        It will be used as the base for conversion.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="5" tag="ref:XBD7:66794:66795">
    If the subject sequence begins with a 'hyphen-minus':
        The value resulting from the conversion will be negated.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="6" tag="ref:XBD7:66795:66797">
    A pointer to the final string will be stored in the object pointed
    to by endptr, provided that endptr is not a null pointer.
    A final string is one or more unrecognized characters, including the
    terminating NUL character of the input string.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="7" tag="ref:XBD7:66800:66802">
    If the subject sequence is empty or does not have the expected form:
        No conversion is performed and the value of nptr will be stored in
        the object pointed to by endptr, provided that endptr is not a
        null pointer.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="8" tag="ref:XBD7:66803:66803">
    This function will not change the setting of errno if successful.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="9" tag="ref:XBD7:66808:66808">
    Upon successful completion, this function will return the converted value, if any.
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="10" tag="ref:XBD7:66808:66809">
    If no conversion could be performed:
        0 will be returned and errno may be set to [EINVAL].
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="11" tag="ref:XBD7:66810:66810">
    If the value of base is not supported:
        0 will be returned and errno will be set to [EINVAL].
  <assertion>
  <assertion id="12" tag="ref:XBD7:66811:66813">
    If the correct value is outside the range of representable values:
        {LONG_MIN}, {LONG_MAX}, will be returned (according to the sign
        of the value), and errno set to [ERANGE].
  <assertion>
<assertions>

