<assertions>
  <assertion id="1" tag="ref:XSH6:34765:34767">
	pthread_rwlock_rdlock( ) function shall apply a read lock to the
	read-write lock referenced by rwlock. The calling thread acquires
	the read lock if a writer does not hold the lock and there are
	no writers blocked on the lock.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="2" tag="ref:XSH8:{System Interfaces:pthread_rwlock_rdlock:DESCRIPTION}">
	If the Thread Execution Scheduling option is supported,
	and the threads that hold or are blocked on the lock are
	executing with the scheduling policies SCHED_FIFO or SCHED_RR,
	the calling thread shall not acquire the lock if a writer
	holds the lock or if the calling thread does not already hold
	a read lock and writers of higher or equal priority are blocked
	on the lock; otherwise, the calling thread shall acquire the lock.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="3" tag="ref:XSH6:34772:34775">
   	If the Threads Execution Scheduling option is supported, and the threads
	involved in the lock are executing with the SCHED_SPORADIC scheduling policy,
	the calling thread shall not acquire the lock if a writer holds the lock or
	if writers of higher or equal priority are blocked on
	the lock; otherwise, the calling thread shall acquire the lock.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="4" tag="ref:XSH6:34792:34794">
  	If a signal is delivered to a thread waiting for a read-write lock for reading,
	upon return from the signal handler the thread resumes waiting for the read-write
	lock for reading as if it was not interrupted.
  </assertion>

<assertion id="5" tag="ref:XSH6:34781:34783">
	A thread may hold multiple concurrent read locks on 'rwlock' and the application shall
	ensure that the thread will perform matching unlocks for each read lock.
</assertion>

  <assertion id="6" tag="ref:XSH6:34796:34797">
  	If successful, the pthread_rwlock_rdlock( ) function shall return zero;
	otherwise, an error number shall be returned to indicate the error.
	These functions shall not return an error code of [EINTR].
  </assertion>
</assertions>
