<assertions>
  <assertion id="1" tag="ref:XSH6:25180:25190">
mmap( ) function shall establish a mapping between the address space of
the process at an address pa for len bytes to the memory object represented
by the file descriptor fildes at offset off for len bytes.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="2" tag="ref:XSH6:25191:25196">
If fildes represents a typed memory object opened with either the
POSIX_TYPED_MEM_ALLOCATE flag or the POSIX_TYPED_MEM_ALLOCATE_CONTIG
flag, the memory object to be mapped shall be that portion of the typed memory object allocated.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="3" tag="ref:XSH6:25197:25199">
mapping established by mmap( ) shall replace any previous mappings for
those whole pages containing any part of the address space.
  </assertion>

  <assertion id="4" tag="ref:XSH6:25203:25204">
TYM The mmap( ) function shall be supported for regular files, shared memory objects, and typed
memory objects. Support for any other type of file is unspecified.
  </assertion>

<assertion id="5" tag="ref:XSH6:25206:25216">
The prot shall be either PROT_NONE or the bitwise-
inclusive OR of one or more of the other flags in the following table
 PROT_READ Data can be read.
 PROT_WRITE Data can be written.
 PROT_EXEC Data can be executed.
 PROT_NONE Data cannot be accessed.
</assertion>

    <assertion id="6" tag="ref:XSH6:25217:25226">
An implementation may permit accesses other than those specified by prot; however, if the
Memory Protection option is supported, the implementation shall not permit a write to succeed
where PROT_WRITE has not been set or shall not permit any access where PROT_NONE alone
has been set. The implementation shall support at least the following values of prot:
PROT_NONE, PROT_READ, PROT_WRITE, and the bitwise-inclusive OR of PROT_READ and
PROT_WRITE. If the Memory Protection option is not supported, the result of any access that
conflicts with the specified protection is undefined. The file descriptor fildes shall have been
opened with read permission, regardless of the protection options specified. If PROT_WRITE is
specified, the application shall ensure that it has opened the file descriptor fildes with write
permission unless MAP_PRIVATE is specified in the flags parameter as described below.
  </assertion>

    <assertion id="7" tag="ref:XSH6:25236:25244">
It is implementation-defined whether MAP_FIXED shall be supported. MAP_FIXED shall be
supported on XSI-conformant systems.
MAP_SHARED and MAP_PRIVATE describe the disposition of write references to the memory
object. If MAP_SHARED is specified, write references shall change the underlying object. If
MAP_PRIVATE is specified, modifications to the mapped data by the calling process shall be
visible only to the calling process and shall not change the underlying object. It is unspecified
whether modifications to the underlying object done after the MAP_PRIVATE mapping is
established are visible through the MAP_PRIVATE mapping. Either MAP_SHARED or
MAP_PRIVATE can be specified, but not both. The mapping type is retained across fork( ).
  </assertion>

    <assertion id="8" tag="ref:XSH6:25245:25260">
When fildes represents a typed memory object opened with either the
POSIX_TYPED_MEM_ALLOCATE flag or the POSIX_TYPED_MEM_ALLOCATE_CONTIG
flag, mmap( ) shall, if there are enough resources available, map len bytes allocated from the
corresponding typed memory object which were not previously allocated to any process in any
processor that may access that typed memory object.
  </assertion>

    <assertion id="9" tag="ref:XSH6:25261:25264">
When MAP_FIXED is set in the flags argument, the implementation is informed that the value of
pa shall be addr, exactly. If MAP_FIXED is set, mmap( ) may returnMAP_FAILED and set errno to
[EINVAL]. If a MAP_FIXED request is successful, the mapping established by mmap( ) replaces
any previous mappings for the process' pages in the range [pa,pa+len).
  </assertion>

    <assertion id="10" tag="ref:XSH6:25265:25271">
When MAP_FIXED is not set, the implementation uses addr in an implementation-defined
manner to arrive at pa. The pa so chosen shall be an area of the address space that the
implementation deems suitable for a mapping of len bytes to the file. All implementations
interpret an addr value of 0 as granting the implementation complete freedom in selecting pa,
subject to constraints described below. A non-zero value of addr is taken to be a suggestion of a
process address near which the mapping should be placed. When the implementation selects a
value for pa, it never places a mapping at address 0, nor does it replace any extant mapping.
  </assertion>

    <assertion id="11" tag="ref:XSH6:25272:25281">
The off argument is constrained to be aligned and sized according to the value returned by
sysconf( ) when passed _SC_PAGESIZE or _SC_PAGE_SIZE. When MAP_FIXED is specified, the
 application shall ensure that the argument addr also meets these constraints. The
implementation performs mapping operations over whole pages. Thus, while the argument len
need not meet a size or alignment constraint, the implementation shall include, in any mapping
operation, any partial page specified by the range [pa,pa+len).
The system shall always zero-fill any partial page at the end of an object. Further, the system
shall never write out any modified portions of the last page of an object which are beyond its
MPR end. References within the address range starting at pa and continuing for len bytes to whole
pages following the end of an object shall result in delivery of a SIGBUS signal.
  </assertion>

    <assertion id="12" tag="ref:XSH6:25284:25286">
The mmap( ) function shall add an extra reference to the file associated with the file descriptor
fildes which is not removed by a subsequent close( ) on that file descriptor. This reference shall be
removed when there are no more mappings to the file.
  </assertion>

      <assertion id="13" tag="ref:XSH6:25287:25290">
The st_atime field of the mapped file may be marked for update at any time between the mmap( )
call and the corresponding munmap( ) call. The initial read or write reference to a mapped region
shall cause the file's st_atime field to be marked for update if it has not already been marked for
update.
  </assertion>

      <assertion id="14" tag="ref:XSH6:25291:25296">
The st_ctime and st_mtime fields of a file that is mapped with MAP_SHARED and PROT_WRITE
shall be marked for update at some point in the interval between a write reference to the
mapped region and the next call to msync( ) with MS_ASYNC or MS_SYNC for that portion of
the file by any process.
  </assertion>

      <assertion id="15" tag="ref:XSH6:25301:25303">
If mmap( ) fails for reasons other than [EBADF], [EINVAL], or [ENOTSUP], some of the
mappings in the address range starting at addr and continuing for len bytes may have been
unmapped.
  </assertion>


      <assertion id="16" tag="ref:XSH6:25305:25308">
Upon successful completion, the mmap( ) function shall return the address at which the mapping
was placed (pa); otherwise, it shall return a value of MAP_FAILED and set errno to indicate the
error. The symbol MAP_FAILED is defined in the sys/mman.h header. No successful return
from mmap( ) shall return the value MAP_FAILED.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="17" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[EACCES] The fildes argument is not open for read, regardless of the protection specified,
or fildes is not open for write and PROT_WRITE was specified for a
MAP_SHARED type mapping.
	  </assertion>

      <assertion id="18" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25315">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
ML [EAGAIN] The mapping could not be locked in memory, if required by mlockall ( ), due to
a lack of resources.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="19" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[EBADF] The fildes argument is not a valid open file descriptor.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="20" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[EINVAL] The addr argument (if MAP_FIXED was specified) or off is not a multiple of
the page size as returned by sysconf( ), or is considered invalid by the
implementation.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="21" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[EINVAL] The value of flags is invalid (neither MAP_PRIVATE nor MAP_SHARED is
set).
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="22" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[EMFILE] The number of mapped regions would exceed an implementation-defined
limit (per process or per system).
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="23" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[ENODEV] The fildes argument refers to a file whose type is not supported by mmap( ).
	  </assertion>

      <assertion id="24" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[ENOMEM] MAP_FIXED was specified, and the range [addr,addr+len) exceeds that allowed
for the address space of a process; or, if MAP_FIXED was not specified and
there is insufficient room in the address space to effect the mapping.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="25" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
 mmap( ) function shall fail if:
 [ENOMEM] The mapping could not be locked in memory, if required by mlockall ( ),
because it would require more space than the system is able to supply.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="26" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
 [ENOMEM] Not enough unallocated memory resources remain in the typed memory
object designated by fildes to allocate len bytes.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="27" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
 [ENOTSUP] MAP_FIXED or MAP_PRIVATE was specified in the flags argument and the
 implementation does not support this functionality.
 The implementation does not support the combination of accesses requested
 in the prot argument.
     </assertion>

      <assertion id="28" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
 The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
 [ENXIO] Addresses in the range [off,off+len) are invalid for the object specified by fildes.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="29" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
 The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
 [ENXIO] MAP_FIXED was specified in flags and the combination of addr, len, and off is
 invalid for the object specified by fildes.
	  </assertion>

      <assertion id="30" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
 [ENXIO] The fildes argument refers to a typed memory object that is not accessible from
the calling process.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="31" tag="ref:XSH6:25310:25342">
The mmap( ) function shall fail if:
[EOVERFLOW] The file is a regular file and the value of off plus len exceeds the offset
maximum established in the open file description associated with fildes.
      </assertion>

      <assertion id="32">
[EINVAL] The value of len is zero.
      <assertion>
</assertions>

